[
	{
		"front": "Which diety gave birth to Cenaruis, patron god of all druids?",
		"back": "Elune"
	},

	{
		"front": "What is the first name of Malfurion's twin brother?",
		"back": "Illidan"
	},

	{
		"front": "What is Tyrande Whisperwind's title?",
		"back": "High Priestess"
	},

	{
		"front": "Of the Dragon Aspects, who was corrupted by the Nightmare and ultimately killed in Legion?",
		"back": "Ysera"
	},

	{
		"front": "How many boss encounters are there in Legion's Nighthold raid?",
		"back": "10"
	},

	{
		"front": "What is the first name of the Lich King that was romatically involved with sorceress Jaina Proudmoore?",
		"back": "Arthas"
	},

	{
		"front": "The Sanctum of Light is which class's Order Hall and sanctuary?",
		"back": "paladin"
	},

	{
		"front": "Which vendor sells the Grand Expedition Yak aka Transmog Mount?",
		"back": "Uncle Bigpocket"
	},

	{
		"front": "What's the highest reputation level you can reach with Conjurer Margoss?",
		"back": "Best Friend"
	},

	{
		"front": "Which player role typically attracts all the enemy threat and takes the bulk of the damage?",
		"back": "tank"
	}
]